Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Photographs PHOTOS 014
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Black and White Photographs, 1952-2002
  - Sub-Series A: Personalities
    - Pascuito, Joseph: Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Chapter Chairperson, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Perlmutter, Ed: Treasurer, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Perales, Cesar: New York State Social Services Commissioner, 1983, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Pfefferman, Robert: Vice-President Publicity, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Pinkett, Mary: President, then member, New York City Council, 1971-2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Posner, Seymour: New York State Assemblyman, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Pumarejo, Yolanda: Executive Vice-President, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Purnell, Ethel: President Department of Social Services (DSS) NAACP, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Q - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - R - Miscellaneous, 1976-1996 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Rabinowitz, Bobbie: Vice-President Publicity, 1980-1996 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Reubens, Jack: Grievances, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Rivera, Magali: Division of AIDS Services (DAS) Caseworker, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Roberts, Lillian: Associate Director District Council (DC) 37, 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - S - Miscellaneous, 1976-1995 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Santos, Isabel: Supervisor I/Grievances Rep, 1978, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Scheuer, James H.: Congressman, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Schleicher, Linda: Assistant to the President for Public Relations, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Selby, Bertha M.: Associate Treasurer/ Homemaker Chapter Chair, 1978-1981, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Serlin, Tony: Associate Director Negations and Research, 1976-1979, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Severson, Sue: Artist, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Shanker, Albert: President American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Silverio, Ramon: Bronx Caseworker, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Simmons, Paul: Organizer, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Small, Edward: Supervisor I Willis Center, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Smith, Tommy: Organizer, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Sperling, Joe: President, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Spinger, Archie: Delegate Assembly then City Council Member, 1979, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Staffa, Reno: Delegate/Activist, 1976, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Stein, Andrew: New York City Council President, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Styles, Reggie: Organizer, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - T - Miscellaneous, 1976-1996 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Talbutt, John: Executive Assistant, 1982-1998 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Taylor, Annie: Executive Board, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Taylor, Aura: Administration Fund Trustee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Tepedino, Joe: President Social Services Employees Union, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - U - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - V - Miscellaneous, 1978-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Viani, Alan: President Local 371, then Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) Deputy Director, 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - W - Miscellaneous, 1976-1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Waite, David: Chairperson Shelters, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Way, John: Executive Committee, 1988, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Wells, Anthony: Associate Director of Organization, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Whitbeck, David: Treasurer (1967-1968) then aide to Carole Parry, 1967, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Whittaker, Tina: Recreation Aide, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Frezelle: Educational and Welfare Funds Trustee, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Williams, Ira: Vice-President Legislation, 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Williams, Katherine: Fire Salvage Worker, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Williams, Nathanial: Vice-President Organization, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Wright, Bruce: New York State Supreme Court Judge, 1979, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Wurf, Al: Executive Director Council 50, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wurf, Jerry: President, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Y, Z - Miscellaneous, 1981-1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Zinzi, Ralph: New York City Labor Relations' Board Staffer, 1979, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Zises, Linda: Supervisor I/Women's Rights Advocate, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Zurio, Joe: President Local 924, 1982, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series B: Subjects
    - 2 Lafayette Street, 1976, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 80 Lafayette Street, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 81 Jay Street (Brooklyn), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 109 East 16th Street, 1980-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 110 Church Street, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 119 West 31st Street, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 127 West 127th Street (Bronx), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 151 Lawrence Street (Brooklyn), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 241 Church Street, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - 250 Church Street, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 299 Broadway relocated to 60 Hudson Street, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 320 Schermerhorn Street (Brooklyn), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 330 Jay Street (Brooklyn), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 350 Livingston Street (Brooklyn), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 625 Fulton Street, 1982-1983, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 770 Broadway, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - "A Campaign to Remember" Union supported US Holocaust Museum, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Administration for Children's Services (ACS) Orientation, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Adoption and Foster Care Services, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - African-American Day Parades, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) trial of Joe Sperling and Jim McKeon., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Anti-Nuclear Actions, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Arbitration: Lateness, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Archives' Opening, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Asbestos Problems, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Awards: Career Civil Service, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Awards: Civil Service Merit Council, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Awards: Human Resources Administration (HRA), 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Awards: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Awards: International Labor Communications Association (ILCA), 1980s (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Awards: International Labor Press Association (ILPA), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Awards: Labor Press Council of Metropolitan New York, 1977-1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Awards: Labor Press Council of Metropolitan New York, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Awards: National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Awards:100 Year Association, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Awards: TransAfrica Writers' Achievement Award, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Ballot Counting, 1981, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Bargaining, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Bargaining, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Bargaining, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Bargaining, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Bargaining, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Bargaining, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Bargaining, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Bargaining, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Bargaining, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Bargaining, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Bargaining: Pension Reopening, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Bellevue Coalition to Save Our Health Care, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Bellevue Nursery, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Benefit Books, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Benefit Funds: Trustees, Staff, Meetings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Benson and Schmidt v. City of New York, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Bermuda Cruise, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Black and Puerto Rican Caucus, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Black History Month Celebrations, 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Black History Month Celebrations, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Black History Month Celebrations, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Black History Month Celebrations, 1994, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Borough Park Senior Citizens Service Fair, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bread and Roses Project, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bronx Agency for Child Development (ACD), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bronx Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW), 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bronx BCW Fashion Shows, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bronx BCW Fashion Shows, 1981, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bronx Child Welfare Agency (CWA), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bronx Emergency Aid Units, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bronx Fire Salvage Unit, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bronx Office of Child Support Enforcement (OCSE), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bronx Special Services for Children (SSC), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Bureau of Child Support (BCS), 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn BCW, 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn Harmony Youth Days, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn SSC, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn Workshop No. 2, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Bushwick Center, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Case Aides, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Caseworkers interviews by NBC on privatization, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Ceiling Collapse at Vets, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Celebration of monetary victory against Health and Hospital Administration, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Central Labor Council (New York City Central Labor Council), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Channel 5 interviews BCW workers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Chapter Leaders, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Child Welfare Group Facilities, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Christmas Parties, 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Christmas Parties, 1991-1994, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Chrystie Street, 1978, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Cities in Schools Program, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Civil Service Committee, 1989, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1981, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Collective Bargaining Certificate [Signing], 1959 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Collective Bargaining Committee, 1990, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Committee of Concerned Social Workers (CCSW), 1982, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Community Alternative Systems Agency (CASA): Privatization, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Community Board #5 (Bronx), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Community Service Officers (CSO), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Conference: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Legislative, Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Conference: AFSCME Social Service, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Conference: American Public Welfare Association (APWA), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Conference: District Council (DC) 37 "Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions", 1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Conference: DC 37 Education, 1985, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Conference: DC 37 Professional, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Conference: DC 37 "Unions and Professionals: Partners for the Future", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Conference: Future of Social Services, held at DC 37, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Conference: Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC) Chapter, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Conference: Health, Welfare and Pension Plan Educational Conference, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Conference: Homemakers, 1977-1981 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Conference: Human Services, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Conference: International Privatization, Geneva, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Conference: Jobs and Peace, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Conference: National Association of Social Workers (NASW), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Conference: New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Conference: New York State Assembly Puerto Rican/Hispanic Task Force "Somos Uno", 1989-1990, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Conference: Leadership, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Conference: Office of Case Intake and Management (OC``) 29, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Conference: Political Action Committee (PAC), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Conference: PAC, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Conference: PAC, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Conference: PAC, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Conference: PAC, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Conference: SSE, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Conference: Trade Union Unity, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Conference: Women's Health, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1982, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Convention: AFL-CIO Merger, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Convention: AFSCME, 1978-1988 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Convention: AFSCME, 1992, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Convention: AFSCME, 1996, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Convention: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Convention: New York State AFL-CIO, 1982, 1986, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Cornell University Students/Graduates, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Crossroads Residential Treatment Center, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - "Dance Darling Dance" Nat Brown, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - DeKalb Center Events, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1970s, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1990s, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Delegate Assembly Candidates' Night, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Delegate Assembly Holiday Card Contest Winners, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Delegate Assembly Training Sessions, 1974-1988 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Delegate Assembly Training Sessions, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Delegate Assembly Training Sessions, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Demonstration(s), 1960s (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Demonstration: 103 Clinton Street, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Demonstration: Against Social Budget Cuts (Albany), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Demonstration: Against State Budget Cutbacks, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Demonstration: AIDS Clients' Rights, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Demonstration: "America Needs a Raise", 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Demonstration: "America's Children Come First" (Washington, DC), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Demonstration(s): Anti-Apartheid, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Demonstration: Bellevue Hospital Layoffs, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Demonstration: Budget Cuts Protest (Albany), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Demonstration(s): Budget Cuts Protest(s) (New York City), 1991, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Demonstration: Case Aides, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Demonstration: Caseworker Suspension (City Hall), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Demonstration: Catchpole, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Demonstration: Chemical Bank, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Demonstration: Child Welfare, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Demonstration: Child Welfare Agency (CWA) (116 East 31st Street), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Demonstration: CWA Caseworker Abuse (Brooklyn), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Demonstration: CWA Workers (Queens), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Demonstration: Child Welfare Workers (City Hall), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Demonstration: Child Welfare Workers (Staten Island), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Demonstration: Civil Service Tests/Promotions (250 Church Street), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Demonstration: Clericalization of Brooklyn Office of Child Support Enforcement, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Demonstration: Clients at City Hall, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Demonstration: Clients/Caseworkers Non-Residence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Demonstration: Community Service Officers (CSO), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Demonstration: Demand Martin Luther King Jr.'s birthday be made a national holiday (Washington, DC), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Demonstration: Detroit Free Press, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Demonstration: Don't Buy GE Products/Don't Buy Farah, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Demonstration: Grant Square Office, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Demonstration: Harlem Hospital Budget Cuts, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Demonstration: Health and Safety at Gertz Building (Jamaica, Queens), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Demonstration: Health and Safety at 300 Jay Street (Brooklyn), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Demonstration: Health and Safety at 320 Schermerhorn Street (Brooklyn), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Demonstration: Healthcare Reform (Washington, DC), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Demonstration: "Lower Caseloads, Better Service", 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Demonstration: Martin Luther King, Jr. Day (New York City), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Demonstration: Medicaid Cuts Protest, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Demonstration: Men's Shelter, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Demonstration: Mental Health Worker Budget Cuts, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Demonstration: Metropolitan Hospital One-Day, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Demonstration: National Health Hearings, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Demonstration: Non-Residential, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Demonstration: "Open Competition Must Go", 1962 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Demonstration: Oppose Tri-Partite, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Demonstration: Phelps-Dodge, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Demonstration: Privatization of Camp LaGuardia (Orange County), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Demonstration: Privatization Protest (Fort Washington), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Demonstration: Protest Employment Center Opening, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Demonstration: Protesting firings, budget cuts at New York City Human Resources Administration (HRA), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Demonstration: Protesting shooting death of Amadu Dialo (Washington, DC), 2000 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Demonstration: Rehire Pauline Hunt, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Demonstration: "Right to Organize", 2002 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Demonstration: Save Greenpoint Methadone Clinic, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Demonstration: Shelters, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Demonstration: Senior Center Cutbacks (City Hall), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Demonstration: Social Service Commission (SSC) (City Hall), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Demonstration: SSC, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Demonstration: SSC, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Demonstration: SSC, Child Services, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Demonstration(s): Solidarity Day, 1981, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Demonstration: Student Labor Peace (City Hall), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Demonstration: Support Amadu Dialo (One Police Plaza), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Demonstration(s): Support Farm Workers, 1988, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Demonstration: Support Local 1199, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Demonstration: Support Local 1549, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Demonstration: Support Memphis Sanitation Workers, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Demonstration: 371 Against Budget Cuts, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Demonstration: 371 Supports 420 "Save the Hospitals" Campaign, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Dental Office, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Dinkins' Campaign, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Direct Child Care Services Career Day, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - District Council (DC) 37: 40th Anniversary Celebration, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - DC 37: Legislative Brunch, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - DC 37: Lobby Day, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - DC 37: Radio Show, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Division of AIDS Services (DAS), 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Dumpson Sit-In, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - East End Center, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - East Harlem Committee Against Drugs (EHCAD), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Eastchester Community Center Building Conditions, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Election Phone Bank (for Bob Abrams), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Elections, 1982-1994 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Ensley Slate and Administration, 1982-1993 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Exam Prep, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Executive Committee, 1976-1992 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Executive Committee Local 371, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - FETSALUD (Nicaraguan Union of Health Care Workers), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Film Festival Opening, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Fire Salvage Program, 1978-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Five Sax's (Atlanta, Georgia), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Floating Hospital (Model Cities Workers), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Food Program Workers, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Fund Scholarship Award, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - General Officers Election Committee Nominations, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Greenpoint, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Grievances, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Group and Family Services Program, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Harlem Hospital Leak, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Haymarket Martyrs' Monument, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hearings, 1978-1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hearings, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hearings: Emergency Financial Control Board (EFCB), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Hearings: Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Hearings: Home Care, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hearings: Welfare Reform, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - High Schools Adopted by Labor Unions, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Hispanic Heritage Celebrations, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Hispanic Heritage Celebrations, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Holiday Card Contests, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Home Economists: Canning Demonstration, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Home Economists on Roosevelt Island, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Homemakers, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Honors Program Students, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Hospital Care Investigators, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - House Parents, 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Housing Action Week, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Housing Technical Assistance Program, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Human Resources Administration (HRA) Chapter, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - HRA Employee Assistance Program, 1986, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - HRA Employee Recognition Day (25 Years of Service), 1984, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - HRA Health Fair, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - HRA Mobil Unit, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Intro 619, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Intro 904 "Consultant Control Bill", 1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Italian Heritage Celebration, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Jennings Hall Meeting and Closing, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Jewish Heritage Month Celebrations, 1995-1996, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - K-11 Open House, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Kenton Hotel, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Kingsbridge, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Labor Day Parades, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Labor Day Parades, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Labor Day Parades, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Labor Day Parades, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Labor Heritage Foundation Great Labor Arts Exchange, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Labor March on Washington, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Labor Research Association Labor Awards Dinner, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Laconia Avenue Group Home (Bronx), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Legal Assistance, 1976, 1984, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Lincoln Hospital, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Lobby Day in Albany, 1981, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Long Term Care, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 56)